Patricia Blasco

Full-Stack Developer | UI/UX Designer

Cocoa, FL | patriciabee.dev@gmail.com | patriciabee.com | (954)736-6242

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Creative and detail-oriented Web Developer & UI/UX designer with experience in designing and coding user-friendly, mobile-responsive websites & applications of all kinds. Worked through 4 years of purely dedicated learning experience, learning JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, Vue, and Laravel, and creating websites for friends, family, and my community. Ready and eager to pursue new challenges in a company that will allow me to collaborate and grow my skills to deliver visually stunning and accessible websites to the world.

SKILLS

Vue.js | Laravel | PHP | JavaScript | CSS | MySQL | Node.js | Pinia | TailwindCSS BootStrap | Git | Figma | Linux | Windows | Apache | Visual Studio Code

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | UI/UX Designer, freelance

5/2021 - present

- Design, develop and maintain landing pages and portfolio websites using LAMP stack and other technologies and frameworks.
- Collaborate with web designers to replicate websites using mock-up designs.
- Convert website code to be fully responsive across a variety of devices.

Marketing Assistant, Marmont Hill Inc.

2/2019 - 02/2021

- Work from home position directly assisting marketing manager with administrative duties using MS Word and Excel.
- Uploaded art collections to various back-end interfaces for dozens of companies.
- Collaborated with art buyers to set up flash sales for retail websites, keeping an organized calendar of events.

Marketing Coordinator, Oliver Gal Artist Co

2/2015 - 2/2017

- Active collaborator to marketing team, bringing forth new ideas and solutions to various problems, also assisted with creating new themes and collections to offer art buyers.
- Uploaded art collections to various back-end interfaces for dozens of companies.
- Monitor sale sites daily for mistakes and report any issues to marketing team.
- Created new lifestyle images for new products using Photoshop.

EDUCATION *certificates available upon request

Udemy, Build Web Apps with React & Firebase

Udemy, Zero to Mastery - Complete Web & Mobile Designer: UI/UX, Figma, + more

Udemy, Modern JavaScript (Complete guide, from Novice to Ninja)

Udemy, Zero to Mastery - JavaScript: The Advanced Concepts

FreeCodeCamp - Responsive Web Design Certification